isedn.org 2015-03-20

# The Independent Search Engine & Directory Network: ISEDN.ORG

This Privacy Policy covers the ISEDN treatment of personal information that is recorded when you submit your site through our free submission service.

Our privacy policy does not apply to the practices of other companies advertised, or otherwise listed, on the ISEDN web site, nor does it extend to people that ISEDN does not employ or manage.

## Information Collection and Use

Unlike many submission services that charge for site submission and collect personal information as well, ISEDN is a free service. The only information collected during site submission is Name, Email Address, URL, and IP Address.

Your use of ISEDN's submission service constitutes a business relationship wherein we provide a promotion service for your web site(s). In exchange, ISEDN reserves the right to use the contact information collected during site submission to deliver notices regarding changes or updates to our service, to provide free sample newsletters, to inform you of additions to the Jayde Online Network of web sites, or to send announcements and carefully screened offers and information from our partners.

With the exception of autoresponse messages which are sent at the time of submission and contain important site submission results, you may remove yourself from any or all other notice and announcement mailings at anytime using the unsubscribe methods provided in those mailings. Any mailing received from our company is clearly identified and includes at least 2 methods to remove yourself from future mailings. Should you encounter problems in this regard, click here to contact us. Our turnaround time for responding to unsubscribe requests is generally 24 hours.

## Cookies

At this time, cookies are not used on the ISEDN site.

## Security

Your personal information is stored in a protected directory. Access is restricted to ISEDN staff.

## Changes to this Privacy Policy

ISEDN may amend this policy from time to time. If significant changes are made in the way your personal information is used, we will post a prominent announcement on our site notifying you of the change.

## Questions or Suggestions

Contact us with your questions or suggestions here
